<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mild Dermatographia</title>
    <link>https://milddermatographia.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mild Dermatographia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, Mild Dermatographia</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 07:08:23 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://milddermatographia.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Prisoner&#39;s Dilemma for Politicians and Journalists</title>
      <link>https://milddermatographia.com/the-prisoners-dilemma-for-politicians-and-journalists/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 07:08:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://milddermatographia.com/the-prisoners-dilemma-for-politicians-and-journalists/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever watched an interview with a politician or company representative where, instead of answering a seemingly straightforward question, they beat around the bush endlessly? Or spout some empty catch-phrase? It&amp;rsquo;s infuriating. Justin Trudeau does it. Donald Trump does it. It really seems like everyone does it. I&amp;rsquo;ve theorized on why privately in the past, but I think I&amp;rsquo;ve finally figured out why; the prisoner&amp;rsquo;s dilemma.
 The Prisoner&amp;rsquo;s Dilemma According to wikipedia:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Pot Pie</title>
      <link>https://milddermatographia.com/chicken-pot-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 16:32:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://milddermatographia.com/chicken-pot-pie/</guid>
      <description>Like a thing having a gradual and cumulative effect, it was insidious. Harmless at first, then snowballing with ever greater intertia. No one could have imagined the world would end this way. And yet.
It began harmlessly enough. A post appeared on Readit with a link to an ad from Utube. It was 10 minutes, unskipeable, and of a man eating a Chicken Pot Pie. No dialogue, no branding, no effects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should I get a Pet?</title>
      <link>https://milddermatographia.com/should-i-get-a-pet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://milddermatographia.com/should-i-get-a-pet/</guid>
      <description>Pets are pretty darn common in Canada. Some of my friends have dogs. Some have cats. Some have more esoteric pets, like turtles or snakes or lizards. Heck, our family has gone through a few generations of rodents of various families. Despite absolute immersion in a pet-friendly society, I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretty against pet ownership for a few years, for various reasons outlined below. That said, I&amp;rsquo;ve never done the research to really back up (or refute) my position, so this is my shoddy attempt at developing a coherent stance on pets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wanting to love Arch and SwayWM</title>
      <link>https://milddermatographia.com/wanting-to-love-arch-and-swaywm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 21:54:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://milddermatographia.com/wanting-to-love-arch-and-swaywm/</guid>
      <description>I originally wrote a long post about transitioning back from Arch to Ubuntu and how slow everything feels in comparison. I then reinstalled Arch and SwayWM, and couldn&amp;rsquo;t get Firefox to use Wayland, no matter where I placed MOZ_ENABLE_WAYLAND=1 or export MOZ_ENABLE_WAYLAND=1. XWayland programs were a blurry mess. I had managed to get everything working the first time around (sort of), but this time, no amount of DDG or Googling could work it out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hedonic Treadmill is Wrong</title>
      <link>https://milddermatographia.com/the-hedonic-treadmill-is-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 16:19:17 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://milddermatographia.com/the-hedonic-treadmill-is-wrong/</guid>
      <description>According the Wikipedia:
 The hedonic treadmill, also known as hedonic adaptation, is the observed tendency of humans to quickly return to a relatively stable level of happiness despite major positive or negative events or life changes.
 This theory has two major shortcomings which I shall (very very seriously) outline and refute. I will then propose a superior theory.
 Hedonism does not adequately describe the variation of happiness A treadmill is a shit fucking analogy for the &amp;ldquo;spring&amp;rdquo; effect demonstrated above  Hedonism is Big Stupid Refering again to the premier source of absolute truth on the internet:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scholarships</title>
      <link>https://milddermatographia.com/scholarships/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 10:44:31 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://milddermatographia.com/scholarships/</guid>
      <description>Tuition at my university costed about $$10,000$ per year; a steal when compared to lofty American universities like Stanford ($$80,000$), not great when compared to other schools in Canada (around $$6,000-$8,000$), and downright criminal when compared to some European schools (free?). This cost was partially offset by a decent scholarship setup. My entry scholarship was worth $$4,000$ for every year of my degree. Since it was a 5 year degree, this effectively covered $$20,000$ of tuition, or about two-fifths the cost of my degree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two-Factor Authentication</title>
      <link>https://milddermatographia.com/two-factor-authentication/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 21:03:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://milddermatographia.com/two-factor-authentication/</guid>
      <description>My University made 2FA mandatory to access remote resources (such as SolidWorks, electrical labs, etc.) a while ago. Once 2FA was set up, however, it was applied universally; if I want to log into my university email, I need to use 2FA. If I want to check my grades, 2FA. If I want to see my schedule, 2FA. If I want to apply for scholarships, you guessed it, 2FA. There&amp;rsquo;s also no return policy on it either.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Retrospection on University</title>
      <link>https://milddermatographia.com/a-retrospection-on-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 17:31:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://milddermatographia.com/a-retrospection-on-university/</guid>
      <description>I graduated from my Mechanical Engineering and Computer Science program last December. A month later, I&amp;rsquo;m in some bizarre purgatory where I spend my days applying for jobs, flicking through streaming services, and slowly rotting away from the inside. Seeing as I might actually spontaneously combust if I don&amp;rsquo;t do something to keep my brain active, here&amp;rsquo;s some thoughts on my university experience. I&amp;rsquo;m sure this will be followed up with belligerent posts on topics outside my expertise, as per internet convention.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
