<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>society on Mild Dermatographia</title>
    <link>https://milddermatographia.com/blog/society/</link>
    <description>Recent content in society on Mild Dermatographia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, Mild Dermatographia</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 07:08:23 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://milddermatographia.com/blog/society/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Prisoner&#39;s Dilemma for Politicians and Journalists</title>
      <link>https://milddermatographia.com/the-prisoners-dilemma-for-politicians-and-journalists/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 07:08:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://milddermatographia.com/the-prisoners-dilemma-for-politicians-and-journalists/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever watched an interview with a politician or company representative where, instead of answering a seemingly straightforward question, they beat around the bush endlessly? Or spout some empty catch-phrase? It&amp;rsquo;s infuriating. Justin Trudeau does it. Donald Trump does it. It really seems like everyone does it. I&amp;rsquo;ve theorized on why privately in the past, but I think I&amp;rsquo;ve finally figured out why; the prisoner&amp;rsquo;s dilemma.
 The Prisoner&amp;rsquo;s Dilemma According to wikipedia:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should I get a Pet?</title>
      <link>https://milddermatographia.com/should-i-get-a-pet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://milddermatographia.com/should-i-get-a-pet/</guid>
      <description>Pets are pretty darn common in Canada. Some of my friends have dogs. Some have cats. Some have more esoteric pets, like turtles or snakes or lizards. Heck, our family has gone through a few generations of rodents of various families. Despite absolute immersion in a pet-friendly society, I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretty against pet ownership for a few years, for various reasons outlined below. That said, I&amp;rsquo;ve never done the research to really back up (or refute) my position, so this is my shoddy attempt at developing a coherent stance on pets.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
